200 acres of barren farmland, and a dream to harvest in harmony with nature.
The Biggest Little Farm is a documentary film directed by John Chester.
The successes and failures of a couple determined to live in harmony with nature on a farm outside of Los
Angeles are lovingly chronicled by filmmaking farmer John Chester, in this inspiring documentary.
Self - Narrator, played by John Chester.
Self, played by Molly Chester.
Self, played by Beaudie Chester.
The Biggest Little Farm is a 2018 American
documentary film, directed by John Chester.
The film profiles the life of John Chester and his wife Molly as they acquire and
establish themselves on Apricot Lane Farms in Moorpark, California.
The film premiered on September 1, 2018, at the Telluride Film Festival.
It had its second screening at the 2018 Toronto International Film Festival, where it
was named second runner-up for the People's Choice Award: Documentaries.
It was selected as the Opening Night film at Doc NYC in November 2018.
The film was screened as part of the Spotlight Section
at the 2019 Sundance Film Festival.
It also screened at the 29th New Orleans Film Festival on October 24, 2018.
The film was acquired for theatrical distribution by the independent film company
Neon, and was released on May 10, 2019 in Los Angeles and New York.
The film expanded into Austin, Boston, Chicago, Dallas, Denver, Houston, Minneapolis, Nashville, Philadelphia, Phoenix,
Portland, San Diego, San Francisco and Washington, D.C., on May 17 and additional markets throughout May and June.
The film was acquired by The Exchange for international distribution.
A sequel special, The Biggest Little Farm: The
Return, was released in 2022 on Disney+.
The film explores themes of farm, california, social
documentary, farming, sustainability.
The tone is uplifting.